excuse me sir is this your Lamborghini
and what do you do for living out here
in Dubai to be able to afford a
Lamborghini money business you're in the
money business are you in finance yeah
we're in finance are you a business
owner how long have you been an
entrepreneur what's this for I go all
over the world ening the most successful
business owners for the younger
generation could I get one quick minute
with you for the channel real quick yeah
for sure over these eight years what was
the most amount of money that you made
in a single year last year we did about
$12 million $122 million do you come
from a lot of money no I don't eight
years ago we couldn't pay a rent and our
rent was $1,300 and I vote to myself
that I'm never coming to that point
again so you were broke I was broke we
had to sell our wedding jewelry to pay
rent Bros so what was that turning point
to Financial Freedom so let me tell you
this when we couldn't pay a rent we had
no Netflix we had no Spotify we had no
subscriptions at all right because we
knew that okay money's tight we're
starting a business what 9 to5 does is
they'll get the money they'll buy this
they'll buy that they'll get cards debt
whatever my mindset was no okay you know
what I have to save save save invest up
until now bro I have no YouTube premium
nothing are you a buyer or a seller I'm
a great salesman give me a master class
on sales right here best sales advices
let's say are you in Dubai yes you're in
Dubai awesome you like the weather here
Dubai I love the weather you like the
vibe here in Dubai I love the vibe would
you like to own a property here in Dubai
one day I think so you think so right so
you get the yes yes yes you can easy
turned it I think so maybe to a yes so
you got to ask a lot of questions you
got to ask a lot of yes questions the
more you say yes yes yes there's a high
probability at the 4th or fifth time
when I do the ass you're going to say
yes amateur tell Pros ass exactly that's
it